The game continues.
Jigsaw is a horror, mystery film directed by Michael Spierig.
Law enforcement finds itself chasing the ghost of a man dead for over a
decade, embroiled in a diabolical new game that's only just begun.
John Kramer / Jigsaw, played by Tobin Bell.
Logan Nelson, played by Matt Passmore.
Detective Halloran, played by Callum Keith Rennie.
Eleanor Bonneville, played by Hannah Emily Anderson.
Keith Hunt, played by Clé Bennett.
Anna, played by Laura Vandervoort.
Jigsaw is a 2017 American horror film directed by the Spierig
Brothers, and written by Josh Stolberg and Peter Goldfinger.
It is the eighth installment in the Saw film series, following Saw 3D (2010), and stars Matt Passmore, Callum Keith
Rennie, Clé Bennett, and Hannah Emily Anderson, with Tobin Bell returning to his role as John Kramer / Jigsaw.
The plot follows a group of people who find themselves forced to
participate in a series of deadly "games" inside a barn.
Meanwhile, the police investigate a new series of murders that fit the modus operandi
of the eponymous Jigsaw Killer, who has been dead for almost a decade.
Saw 3D was deemed the final installment of the series before Lionsgate commissioned
the production of Jigsaw from a pitch by Stolberg and Goldfinger.
Early development began in 2013 with production officially
starting in 2016 on a budget of $10 million.
The film was released by Lionsgate Films in the
United States on October 27, 2017.
Jigsaw received negative reviews and grossed a
total of $104.2 million worldwide.
It was followed by a standalone installment in the series,
titled Spiral: From the Book of Saw, in 2021.
The film explores themes of sadism, gore, sequel, flashback, torture.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.